http://www.naturalarearugs.com/page/privacy-policy/

Free Shipping
Easy Returns
Most Rugs Made in USA
1-800-661-7847
Search Keyword:
Privacy Policy
At Natural Area Rugs, we value the privacy of our customers and have implemented strict online policies and procedures. Please read our privacy policy to see how we collect and use your information.
Collecting your information
Natural Area Rugs gathers personally identifiable information from visitors who register their information with us. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify, contact or locate you as an individual. Common examples are your name and email address.
Most of this information is necessary. We need your name, telephone numbers, physical address, email address and other billing information to serve you.
The other type of information we collect is known as aggregate information. This information helps us gather advertising and marketing statistics. For example, we can inform advertisers that most people who visit our website are over 25 years old. This information does not disclose any personal information about any of our individual customers.
We use cookies (small portions of data stored on your computer) to keep track of previous visitors and recall some of the information you may have entered.
How we use this information
The personal information we collect is used to process your online order, provide quotes and any other inquiries you might have. Occasionally we may send you an email announcing a special sale or event related to our website. You'll only receive these messages if you opted in, or agreed to receive them.
Generally, we use customer information to analyze website performance, to confirm your order, send you the quote you requested or track aggregate information. Aggregate information helps us to monitor our website and see how different visitors react to the content and design.
Sharing your information with third parties
Natural Area Rugs won't disclose your personal information with anyone outside of our organization.
We may hire third parties to enhance our website or for advertising purposes. These third parties may use cookies or web beacons to measure advertisement effectiveness, but this information is aggregate information and is completely anonymous.
The only time we would share any personal information with a third party is if it were required by law.
Our website may or may not contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content security of other websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read that website's privacy policies, since they may be differ from ours.
Security
Natural Area Rugs has established security measures in our facilities to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of any of the information we collect from you. We implement industry standard security measures for our ISP and standard encryption technology when receiving or transferring customer data to our website.
However, it's important to note that no Internet data transmission can ever be guaranteed 100% secure. Therefore, we can't guarantee the security of any information you transmit using our website. You transmit this information at your own risk.
Natural Area Rugs does not assume responsibility for any illegal or unauthorized access to our systems or those of our partners.
For information about our shopping cart security you can read more here.
Credit Card Security
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of credit card transmissions. This technology encrypts your credit card information.
How to make sure you are on a secure server:
Before entering your personal financial information, there are things you can watch out for to make sure the SSL is active and that you are on a secure server.
Look at the bottom of your browser. Depending on your browser you should see an unbroken key or a closed lock icon. This indicates that your SSL is active and that you are accessing a secure server.
Another security check that is easy to perform is to look up at the URL or location line of your browser. The first characters of a secure server will have changed from "http" to "https."
If your browser doesn't permit communication through secure servers, or you can't seem to access our secure server, just send an email to our Customer Service department. You may also send a fax to (323) 582-1117.
Privacy Policy Changes
This website is maintained and run by the IT department of NaturalAreaRugs.com in Los Angeles, California.
Natural Area Rugs reserves the right to make occasional changes to how we use customer information. Any privacy policy changes will be clearly posted on this page. We recommend that visitors with privacy concerns or questions check this page periodically for updates.
Contact Us
For comments or inquires concerning our privacy police, please do not hesitate to email us using our contact page, or write to us at the address below:
Natural Area Rugs3737 S. Santa Fe Ave.Los Angeles CA 90058
×
